A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review, 1935-1954
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Pegler, Westbrook 1935 September 17, 1 l. (Box 119)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Pegler
- Penguin Books, Ltd. 1939-1943, 8 items (Box 119)
- Pepper, Claude 1939-1954, 15 items (Box 119)
- Pergler, Charles 1938-1945, 27 items (Box 119)
- Perkins, Dexter 1936-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 120)
- Perkins, Frances 1935, 2 items (Box 120)
- Perkins, Maxwell 1935-1939, 8 items (Box 120)
- Perry, Marvin 1936-1954, 27 items (Box 120)
- Perry, Ralph Barton 1941-1954, 25 items (Box 120)
- Peters, John 1938-1940, 26 items (Box 120)
- Peterson, Merrill 1953, 4 items (Box 120)
- Peyre, Henri 1947-1953, 24 items (Box 120)
- Phelps, Robert 1951, 7 items (Box 120)
- Phelps, William Lyon 1936 December 15, 1 l. (Box 120)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Phelps
- Philips, Duncan 1940, 2 items (Box 120)
- Phillips, Thomas Hal 1951-1953, 5 items (Box 120)
- Pierce, Edith Lovejoy 1938-1940, 2 items (Box 120)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Pierce
- Pinckney, Josephine 1936-1947, 13 items (Box 120)
- Pinker and Morrison 1935-1938, ca. 50 items (Box 120)
- Piper, Edwin Ford 1939, 4 items (Box 120)
- Pitter, Ruth 1939-1949, 21 items (Box 120)
- Pittman, Key 1938-1939, 4 items (Box 120)
- Pocket Books, Inc. 1940-1943, 5 items (Box 120)
- Podolsky, Edward 1937-1953, 27 items (Box 120)
- Poe, Clarence 1937, 5 items (Box 120)
- Pol, Heinz 1941, 7 items (Box 120)
- Pollock, Herbert 1946-1949, 21 items (Box 120)
- Pollock, James Kerr 1945-1951, 8 items (Box 120)
- Poole, Sidman 1946 December 5, 1 l. (Box 120)
- Poore, Dudley 1945-1946, 7 items (Box 120)
- Pope, Liston 1953, 4 items (Box 120)
- Porter, Katherine Anne 1936-1954, 19 items (Box 120)
- Potter, Pitman 1952-1953, 15 items (Box 120)
- Pottle, Frederick 1936-1953, 5 items (Box 120)
- Pound, Arthur 1936, 3 items (Box 120)
- Pound, Louise 1945, 7 items (Box 120)
- Powers, Marcella 1945-1948, ca. 50 items (Box 120)
- Powys, Llewelyn 1938-1939, 11 items (Box 120)
- Pozner, Vladimir 1943, 2 items (Box 120)
- Pratt, Agnes, Rothery 1940-1948, 4 items (Box 120)
- Pratt, Fletcher 1954, 8 items (Box 120)
- Pratt, John Lee 1929-1939, 29 items (Box 120)
- Pratt, Theodore 1946, 2 items (Box 120)
- Prentice-Hall, Inc. 1929-1951, 19 items (Box 120)
- Prescott, Joseph 1939-1953, 8 items (Box 120)
- Preston, John Hyde 1940, 3 items (Box 120)
- Price, Frank 1953-1954, 16 items (Box 120)
- Price, R. M. 1939-1941, 7 items (Box 120)
- Princeton University Press 1926-1950, 18 items (Box 120)
- Pritchett, Charles Herman 1942-1952, ca. 50 items (Box 120)
- Mary Pritchett-Barbaba Brandt 1940-1950, ca. 50 items (Box 120)
- Pritt, Denis Nowell 1939, 9 items (Box 120)
- Prokosch, Frederic 1937-1944, 13 items (Box 120)
- Pudney, John 1947-1948, 9 items (Box 120)
- Pugh, Lamont 1951, 2 items (Box 120)
- Puleston, William 1942, 2 items (Box 120)
- Pusey, Merlo 1954, 2 items (Box 120)
- Pusey, Nathan 1954, 2 items (Box 120)
- G.P. Putnam's Sons 1926-1950, 31 items (Box 120)
- Miscellaneous P 1935-1954, ca. 100 items (Box 121)
  Miscellaneous authors, Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review.
- Quennell, Peter 1947-1948, 3 items (Box 122)
- Quigley, Harold 1936-1952, ca. 50 items (Box 122)
- Quillian, William 1953 March 18, 1 l. (Box 122)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Quillian
- Quinn, Kerker 1934-1944, ca. 50 items (Box 122)
- Miscellaneous Q 1937-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 122)
- Radin, Max 1945-1949, 23 items (Box 122)
- Ramey, Lee 1939, 12 items (Box 122)
- Randall, James Garfield 1938-1950, 10 items (Box 122)
- Randall-Mills, Elizabeth 1936-1952, 9 items (Box 122)
- Random House 1935-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 122)
- Ransom, John Crowe 1930-1949, ca. 50 items (Box 122)
- Raper, Arthur 1939-1940, 20 items (Box 122)
- Rapport, Leonard 1936-1949, ca. 50 items (Box 122)
- Rascoe, Burton 1936-1941, 3 items (Box 122)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Rascoe
- Ratchford, Benjamin Ulysses 1947-1951, 5 items (Box 122)
- Ray, Gordon 1952-1954, 19 items (Box 122)
- Read, Herbert 1936, 13 items (Box 122)
- Reader's Digest 1931-1948, ca. 50 items (Box 122)
- Redman, Ben Ray 1943-1947, 3 items (Box 122)
- Reece, Byron Herbert 1943-1951, 6 items (Box 122)
- Reed, Stanley 1939 March 30, 1 l. (Box 122)
- Reese, George 1942, 3 items (Box 122)
- Reese, Lizette Woodworth 1935 July 21, 1 l. (Box 122)
- Reeves, Katherine 1951-1954, 16 items (Box 122)
- Reid, Fergus 1935-1939, 12 items (Box 122)
- Reik, Theodor 1938, 4 items (Box 122)
- Reither, Joseph 1937-1943, 26 items (Box 122)
- Reitzel, William 1952-1953, 9 items (Box 122)
- Remarque, Eric Maria 1939 October 26, 1 l. (Box 122)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Remarque
- Reston, James 1950, 2 items (Box 122)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Reston
- Reuther, Walter 1954 September 2, 1 l. (Box 122)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Reuther
- Review of Reviews 1930-1934, 7 items (Box 122)
- Rexroth, Kenneth 1951, 2 items (Box 122)
- Reynal and Hitchcock, Inc. 1938-1946, 30 items (Box 122)
- Paul R. Reynolds and Son 1936-1950, 18 items (Box 122)
- Rhodes, Peter 1945, 4 items (Box 123)
- Ribble, Frederick 1939-1952, 11 items (Box 123)
- Rice, Cale Young 1939-1942, 6 items (Box 123)
- Rice, Howard Crosby 1937-1938, 4 items (Box 123)
- Rice, Laban Lacy 1950, 3 items (Box 123)
- Rice, Virginia 1937-1953, 12 items (Box 123)
- Rice, Warner 1951, 4 items (Box 123)
- Rich, Adrienne 1949-1951, 8 items (Box 123)
- Richards, Edward A. 1936, 2 items (Box 123)
- Richards, Ivor Armstrong 1935-1937, 2 items (Box 123)
- Richardson, Dorothy 1952-1954, 9 items (Box 123)
- Richardson, Eudora Ramsay 1950-1951, 4 items (Box 123)
- Richardson, Ransom Lloyd 1942-1946, 8 items (Box 123)
- Richey, Homer 1949-1950, 12 items (Box 123)
- Riddick, Floyd 1936-1937, 10 items (Box 123)
- Ridenour, Louis 1954, 10 items (Box 123)
- Ridler, Anne 1949-1951, 11 items (Box 123)
- Riegel, Oscar Wetherhold 1938, 14 items (Box 123)
- Riezler, Kurt 1942, 8 items (Box 123)
- Riggs, Arthur Stanley 1936-1952, 32 items (Box 123)
- Rinehart and Company 1951, 4 items (Box 123)
- Ripley, Katherine 1938, 3 items (Box 123)
- Rippy, James Fred 1937-1938, 8 items (Box 123)
- Rivera, Diego 1944 December 14, 1 l. (Box 123)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Rivera
- Roberts, C.B. 1936, 6 items (Box 123)
- Roberts, Elizabeth Madox 1939-1940, 8 items (Box 123)
- Roberts, John Hawley 1936-1941, ca. 50 items (Box 123)
- Robertson, John 1937 February 16, 1 l. (Box 123)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Robertson
- Robin, Max 1936-1952, 31 items (Box 123)
- Robinson, Edgar 1945, 4 items (Box 123)
- Robinson, Edwin Arlington 1925, 2 items (Box 123)
  2 ALS to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Robinson, Geroid 1953, 2 items (Box 123)
- Rockefeller, John Davidson, Jr. 1928 October 16, 1 l. (Box 123)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Rockefeller
- Roditi, Edouard 1944-1953, 15 items (Box 123)
- Roethke, Theodore 1936-1945, 29 items (Box 123)
- Rogers, Katherine 1941, 5 items (Box 123)
- Rogers, Lindsay 1938-1949, 30 items (Box 123)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor, Reps. of 1938-1939, 17 items (Box 123)
- Rose, D.N. 1949 June 21, 1 l. (Box 123)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Rose
- Rose, Turner 1936-1947, 16 items (Box 123)
- Roseboro, Viola 1939, 2 items (Box 123)
- Rosenberger, Francis Coleman 1939-1953, items (Box 123)
- Roskolenko, Harry 1937-1951, 19 items (Box 123)
- Ross, Dan 1938, 3 items (Box 123)
- Ross, E.C. 1943-1947, 11 items (Box 123)
- Ross, Margaret 1951, 7 items (Box 123)
- Ross, William 1951 June 29, 1 l. (Box 123)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Ross
- Rossi, Mario 1943-1953, 14 items (Box 123)
- Rosten, Norman 1940, 3 items (Box 123)
- Rostow, Eugene 1938-1952, ca. 50 items (Box 123)
- Rostow, Walt 1938, 2 items (Box 123)
- Roucek, Joseph 1939-1940, 9 items (Box 123)
- Rourke, Constance 1937, 8 items (Box 123)
- Rourke, Thomas 1941-1942, 7 items (Box 123)
- Rouse, Blair 1936-1952, 10 items (Box 123)
- Rowe, David 1947-1950, 25 items (Box 123)
- Roy, Dunbar 1924-1932, 11 items (Box 123)
- Rubin, Louis, Jr. 1944-1954, 9 items (Box 124)
- Rucker, William 1924-1936, 10 items (Box 124)
- Rukeyser, Muriel 1939, 3 items (Box 124)
- Rushton, Allen 1948, 5 items (Box 124)
- Rushton, Peters 1941-1948, 7 items (Box 124)
- Rusk, Dean 1953, 2 items (Box 124)
- Rusk, William Sener 1936-1945, 33 items (Box 124)
- Russell, Bertrand 1940-1952, 22 items (Box 124)
- Russell, Henry Norris 1940, 9 items (Box 124)
- Russell and Volkening, Inc. 1939-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 124)
- Rutledge, Archibald 1936-1951, 24 items (Box 124)
- Ruttenberg, Harold 1940, 17 items (Box 124)
- Ryan, John 1939, 8 items (Box 124)
- Ryan, Thomas, Reps. of 1924-1929, 10 items (Box 124)
- Miscellaneous R 1935-1954, ca. 900 items (Box 124 & 125)
- Sachs, Oscar 1939-1940, 2 items (Box 125)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Sachs
- Sackville-West, V. 1937, 5 items (Box 125)
- Salomez, John 1941-1942, 9 items (Box 125)
- Saltonstall, Leverett 1952, 2 items (Box 125)
- Sandburg, Carl 1938-1949, 9 items (Box 125)
- Sanders, Sydney 1938-1953, 12 items (Box 125)
- Sansom, William 1948 June 16, 1 l. (Box 125)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Sansom
- Sargent, Porter 1936-1943, 20 items (Box 125)
- Saroyan, William 1938-1939, 4 items (Box 125)
- Sarton, George 1935-1952, 3 items (Box 125)
- Sarton, May 1938-1940, 19 items (Box 125)
- Sass, Herbert Ravenal 1936, 4 items (Box 125)
- Satenstein, Sidney 1937-1953, ca. 50 items (Box 125)
- Saturday Review 1935-1943, 8 items (Box 125)
- Saunders, Marion 1939-1954, ca. 100 items (Box 125)
- Saxon, Lylé 1936 January 8, 1 l. (Box 125)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Saxon
- Schack, William 1941-1948, 21 items (Box 125)
- Scham, Wilbur 1948 July 30, 1 item (Box 125)
- Scheffer, Paul 1938, 9 items (Box 125)
- Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr. 1938-1951, 8 items (Box 125)
- Schmeckebier, Laurence 1939, 2 items (Box 125)
- Schoeck, R. J. 1951-1952, 10 items (Box 125)
- Schoolcraft, John 1936-1937, 19 items (Box 125)
- Schorer, Mark 1937-1951, ca. 50 items (Box 125)
- Schorske, Carl 1947, 15 items (Box 125)
- Schramm, Wilbur 1938-1945, ca. 50 items (Box 125)
- Schubert, David 1936-1943, 33 items (Box 125)
- Schubert, Paul 1942-1946, 26 items (Box 125)
- Schuman, Frederick 1944-1945, 5 items (Box 125)
- Schuyler, Jack 1940-1948, 12 items (Box 125)
- Schuyler, Robert Livingston 1943, 2 items (Box 125)
- Schwarzenberger, Georg 1944-1947, 12 items (Box 126)
- Schwellenbach, Lewis 1938 May 7, 1 l. (Box 126)
- Scott, Frederic 1931, 4 items (Box 126)
- Scott, Winfield Townley 1949-1954, 26 items (Box 126)
- Charles Scribner's Sons 1928-1953, ca. 50 items (Box 126)
- Scruggs, Anderson 1936-1946, 7 items (Box 126)
- Scruggs, Philip 1938-1954, 24 items (Box 126)
- Sedgwick, Ellery 1948, 3 items (Box 126)
- Sen, Binay Ranjam 1952 August 14, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Sen (Box 126)
- Seymour, Charles 1943-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 126)
- Shane, Charles 1953 August 5, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Shane (Box 126)
- Shannon, Edgar, Jr. 1946, 2 items (Box 126)
- Shapiro, Karl 1939 September 28, 1 l. (Box 126)
- Sharp, Dolph 1949-1951, 15 items (Box 126)
- Shaw, George Bernard 1939 October 16, 1 l. (Box 126)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Shaw
- Shaw, Louis Agassiz, 2nd 1937-1950, 26 items (Box 126)
- Sheean, Vincent 1939-1954, 34 items (Box 126)
- Sheldon, Edward 1930-1943, 3 items (Box 126)
- Shepardson, Whitney 1949, 2 items (Box 126)
- Shepperson, Archibald 1936-1954, 43 items (Box 126)
- Shepperson, Archibald 1945-1946, 20 items (Box 126)
  Personal correspondence, with various people, chiefly re: graduate school recommendations
- Shippee, Lester 1950 September 28, 1 l. (Box 126)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Shippee
- Shone, Patric, Reps. of 1950, 8 items (Box 126)
- Short, Christopher 1941-1947, 5 items (Box 126)
- Shotwell, James 1939-1945, 6 items (Box 126)
- Shyrock, Richard 1950, 2 items (Box 126)
- Sibley, Harper 1935, 2 items (Box 126)
- Siegfried, André November 12, 1 l. (Box 126)
- Silsbee, Nathaniel 1942-1943, 26 items (Box 126)
- Silver, Rollo 1950, 2 items (Box 126)
- Simkins, Francis 1953, 8 items (Box 126)
- Simon and Schuster 1926-1949, 19 items (Box 126)
- Simpson, Lesley Byrd 1952-1953, 15 items (Box 126)
- Simpson, Louis 1950-1952, 3 items (Box 126)
- Simpson, Smith 1949-1951, 14 items (Box 126)
- Sims, Lydel 1937-1954, 11 items (Box 126)
- Singh, Anup 1941, 12 items (Box 126)
- Sinnott, Edmund 1950 May 25, 1 l. (Box 126)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Sinnott
- Slemp, Campbell Bascom 1931-1935, 8 items (Box 126)
- Slichter, Sumner 1948-1950, 8 items (Box 126)
- William Sloane Associates 1946-1952, 20 items (Box 126)
- Slochower, Harry 1937-1941, 15 items (Box 126)
- Slote, Bernice 1946-1951, 8 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Bernard 1940-1941, 9 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Blackwell 1947, 7 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Carleton Sprague 1940-1941, 17 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Charles Alphonso 1954, 5 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Charles William 1937-1954, 16 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Frank 1954, 3 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Horatio 1942, 2 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Lillian 1938 May 12, 1 l. (Box 126)
- Smith, Thomas Vernor 1946-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Warren 1949-1953, 11 items (Box 126)
- Smith, Wilfred 1954, 2 items (Box 126)
- Smyth, Howard McGaw 1949-1953, 35 items (Box 126)
- Smythe, Daniel 1936-1947, 23 items (Box 126)
- Snavely, Tipton Ray 1937-1944, 3 items (Box 126)
- Snow, Wilbert 1937-1950, 11 items (Box 126)
- Soffner, Heinz 1941-1942, 19 items (Box 127)
- Sontag, Raymond 1953, 5 items (Box 127)
- Soule, George 1936-1944, 22 items (Box 127)
- Southall, James 1939, 5 items (Box 127)
- Southern Conference for Human Welfare 1938-1940, 21 items (Box 127)
- Souvarine, Boris 1941-1943, 20 items (Box 127)
- Spaak, Paul-Henri 1952-1953, 3 items (Box 127)
- Sparrow, Carroll Mason 1936-1941, 5 items (Box 127)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Sparrow
- Spears, Monroe 1953 September 29, 1 l. (Box 127)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Spears
- Spencer, Elizabeth n.d., 1 l. (Box 127)
  TNS, to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Spencer, Theodore 1939-1947, 6 items (Box 127)
- Spender, Stephen 1939-1947, 2 items (Box 127)
- Sperry, Willard 1948-1952, 32 items (Box 127)
- Spicer, George 1952, 2 items (Box 127)
- Spiller, Robert 1946-1953, 14 items (Box 127)
- Spilman, Robert 1939-1941, 10 items (Box 127)
- Spingarn, Lawrence 1942-1954, 21 items (Box 127)
- Spykman, Nicholas 1943, 3 items (Box 127)
- Stace, Walter Terence 1953, 2 items (Box 127)
- Stallman, Robert Wooster 1944-1951, 19 items (Box 127)
- Stark, Louis 1946, 7 items (Box 127)
- Starke, Aubrey 1946, 7 items (Box 127)
- Starkie, Enid 1939 September 22, 1 l. (Box 127)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Starkie
- Sstarkie, Walter 1947, 4 items (Box 127)
- Starrett, Vincent 1938-1940, 3 items (Box 127)
- Stauffer, Donald 1936-1951, 39 items (Box 127)
- Stead, William Force 1938-1945, 6 items (Box 127)
- Stearns, Florence Dickinson 1938-1951, 3 items (Box 127)
- Steel Workers Organizing Committee 1939-1940, 3 items (Box 127)
- Steele, Charles 1932-1934, 16 items (Box 127)
- Steelman, John 1944-1945, 8 items (Box 127)
- Stegner, Wallace 1938-1949, ca. 50 items (Box 127)
- Stein, Gunther 1945-1946, 21 items (Box 127)
- Steinbeck, John 1939 June 18, 1 l. (Box 127)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Steinbeck
- Stephens, James 1938-1939, 5 items (Box 127)
- Stephenson, Wendell 1950-1953, 18 items (Box 127)
- Stern, Philip Van Doren 1940-1942, ca. 50 items (Box 127)
- Stettinius, Edward, Jr. 1924-1947, 25 items (Box 127)
- Stevenson, Adlai 1952-1954, 3 items (Box 127)
- Stevenson, Lionel 1936-1944, 20 items (Box 127)
- Stewart, George 1943-1953, 7 items (Box 127)
- Stewart, J.I.M. 1953, 3 items (Box 127)
- Stewart, Randall 1948-1954, 27 items (Box 127)
- Still, James 1936-1948, 31 items (Box 127)
- Stimpson, Henry 1939, 2 items (Box 127)
- Stockwell, Richard 1947-1948, 8 items (Box 127)
- Stoddard, George 1947-1948, 3 items (Box 127)
- Stone, Charles 1935-1940, 12 items (Box 127)
- Stone, I.F. & assoc. 1938-1949, ca. 50 items (Box 127)
- Stone, William 1939, 2 items (Box 127)
- Storck, John 1943, 9 items (Box 127)
- Storm, Hans Otto 1939, 2 items (Box 127)
- Stout, Hiram 1953-1954, 16 items (Box 127)
- Strassman, Toni 1937-1954, 14 items (Box 128)
- Strayer, Joseph 1950-1951, 6 items (Box 128)
- Strobel, Marion 1945 March 19, 1 l. (Box 128)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Strobel
- Strode, Hudson 1940-1944, 11 items (Box 128)
- Strong, Frank 1953, 4 items (Box 128)
- Strout, Cushing 1951-1954, 16 items (Box 128)
- Stuart, Graham 1941-1942, 21 items (Box 128)
- Hope Stuart Associates 1946-1947, 10 items (Box 128)
- Stuart, Jesse 1936-1951, ca. 50 items (Box 128)
- Stubbs, W.B. 1954, 2 items (Box 128)
- Styron, William 1946, 2 items (Box 128)
- Sidney and Edith Sulkin 1938-1948, 7 items (Box 128)
- Summers, Hollis 1950-1954, 7 items (Box 128)
- Sun-Yat-Sen, Madame 1936-1938, 2 items (Box 128)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Madame Sun
- Swan, Emma 1945, 2 items (Box 128)
- Swanson, Claude 1935, 2 items (Box 128)
- Swem, Earl Gregg 1941 January 24, 1 l. (Box 128)
- Swing, Raymond 1942, 2 items (Box 128)
- Swisher, Carl 1946, 2 items (Box 128)
- Sydnor, Charles 1948, 3 items (Box 128)
- Sypher, Wylie 1949-1950, 11 items (Box 128)
- Miscellaneous S 1935-1954, ca. 1300 items (Box 128 & 129)
- Tabouis, Geneviève 1939, 13 items (Box 130)
- Taft, Charles 1936-1954, 32 items (Box 130)
- Taft, William Howard 1925 May 11, 1 l. (Box 130)
- Taggard, Genevieve 1941-1946, 12 items (Box 130)
- Tate, Allen 1930-1945, ca. 50 items (Box 130)
- Tate, Caroline Gordon 1937-1940, 6 items (Box 130)
- Tarbell, Ida 1937, 3 items (Box 130)
- Tawney, Richard Henry 1940-1942, 5 items (Box 130)
- Taylor, Eleanor Ross January 28, 1 l. (Box 130)
- Taylor, Fielding Lewis 1935-1940, 15 items (Box 130)
- Taylor, George E. 1949-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 130)
- Taylor, Olivia 1939, 2 items (Box 130)
- Taylor, Peter 1949-1954, 6 items (Box 130)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1924-1940, ca. 50 items (Box 130)
- Taylor, Tazewell 1935-1939, 14 items (Box 130)
- Templin, E.H. 1937-1948, ca. 50 items (Box 130)
- Terral, Rufus 1946-1947, 4 items (Box 130)
- Tetley, Gerald 1944-1950, 4 items (Box 130)
- Theobald, John 1938-1945, 11 items (Box 130)
- Thom, Decourcy 1925-1933, 22 items (Box 130)
- Thomas, Dylan 1947-1948, 2 items (Box 130)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Thomas
- Thomas, Gilbert 1950, 6 items (Box 130)
- Thomas, Keith 1937-1943, 21 items (Box 130)
- Thomas, Lewis 1948, 7 items (Box 130)
- Thomas, Lowell 1936 December 15, 1 l. (Box 130)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Thomas
- Thomas, Norman 1931 January 17, 1 l. (Box 130)
- Thomas, Rosemary 1937-1946, 2 items (Box 130)
- Thompson, Charles 1937-1938, 14 items (Box 130)
- Thompson, Lawrance 1937, 6 items (Box 130)
- Thompson, Margaret 1954, 5 items (Box 130)
- Thompson, Morton 1939-1940, 3 items (Box 130)
- Thompson, Randall 1941-1944, 8 items (Box 130)
- Thompson, Stith 1949, 4 items (Box 130)
- Thompson, Virgil 1950-1951, 2 items (Box 130)
- Thompson, Wade 1951-1952, 6 items (Box 130)
- Thorp, Willard 1942-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 130)
- Tillich, Paul 1953-1954, 3 items (Box 130)
- Tillery, Floyd 1937-1940, 8 items (Box 130)
- Time Magazine 1930-1950, 6 items (Box 130)
- Tinker, Edward Larocque 1954, 3 items (Box 130)
- Todrin, Boris 1937-1938, 8 items (Box 130)
- Toland, Edmund 1939, 4 items (Box 130)
- Toller, Ernest 1939, 7 items (Box 130)
- Torrence, Ridgely 1935-1939, 8 items (Box 130)
- Towers, Frances 1947, 2 items (Box 130)
- Towles, Oliver 1938, 3 items (Box 130)
- Tree, Ronald 1929-1939, 30 items (Box 130)
- Treece, Henry 1951 June 22, 1 l. (Box 130)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Treece
- Trigg, Emma Gray 1937-1953, 6 items (Box 130)
- Trilling, Lionel 1945-1951, 4 items (Box 130)
- Troubetzkoy, Amélie Rives 1935-1942, 5 items (Box 130)
- Truman, Harry 1954, 2 items (Box 130)
- Tucker, Beverley 1944, 3 items (Box 131)
- Tunstall, Robert 1925-1932, 29 items (Box 131)
- Turner, Howard 1953-1954, 4 items (Box 131)
- Turner, Violet 1937-1944, 6 items (Box 131)
- Tuttle, Stephen 1944-1953, 16 items (Box 131)
- Tydings, Millard 1935 June 20, 1 l. (Box 131)
- Tyler, Dorothy 1936-1950, 24 items (Box 131)
- Miscellaneous T 1935-1954, ca. 550 items (Box 131)
- Untermeyer, Louis 1939-1945, 15 items (Box 131)
- Uzzell, Thomas 1932-1948, 25 items (Box 131)
- Miscellaneous U 1935-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 131)
- Vagts, Alfred 1939-1942, ca. 50 items (Box 132)
- Valentini, E.E. 1939, 3 items (Box 132)
- Valéry, Paul, Representative of 1938, 2 items (Box 132)
- Van Alen, Eleanor 1941, 6 items (Box 132)
- Vance, Earl 1945-1947, ca. 50 items (Box 132)
- Vance, Rupert 1939-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 132)
- Vandenbosch, Amry 1948-1952, 20 items (Box 132)
- Vandenburg, Arthur 1940, 2 items (Box 132)
- Vandercook, John 1943, 2 items (Box 132)
- Van der Post, Laurens 1953, 2 items (Box 132)
- Van Doren, Carl 1925-1943, 3 items (Box 132)
- Van Doren, Irita 1935-1939, 4 items (Box 132)
- Van Doren, Mark 1936-1951, ca. 50 items (Box 132)
- Vanguard Press 1936-1948, ca. 50 items (Box 132)
- Van Langehove, Fernand, Representative of 1951, 2 items (Box 132)
- Van Paassen, Pierre 1945, 5 items (Box 132)
- Vazakas, Byron 1938-1948, 5 items (Box 132)
- Vazquez, Alvaro 1942, 2 items (Box 132)
- Venable, Vernon 1937-1938, ca. 50 items (Box 132)
- Verner, Coolie 1953 June 22, 1 l. (Box 132)
- Viereck, George 1952, 2 items (Box 132)
- Viereck, Peter 1940-1951, 32 items (Box 132)
- Viking Press 1936-1949, ca. 50 items (Box 132)
- Viner, Jacob 1946, 2 items (Box 132)
- Viton, Albert 1939-1947, ca. 50 items (Box 132)
- Vivian, John 1937-1949, 7 items (Box 132)
- Vodenlitch, Leonidas 1938, 8 items (Box 132)
- Vogt, William 1954, 2 items (Box 132)
- Von Auw, Ivan, Jr. 1941, 3 items (Box 132)
- Miscellaneous V 1935-1954, ca. 200 items (Box 132)
- Wade, John Donald 1936-1946, 16 items (Box 133)
- Wadsworth, James, Jr. 1935 September 17, 1 l. (Box 133)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Wadsworth
- Wagenknecht, Edward 1935-1948, 24 items (Box 133)
- Wagner, Geoffrey 1948-1954, 14 items (Box 133)
- Wagner, Robert 1938-1939, 3 items (Box 133)
- Waley, Arthur 1939, 2 items (Box 133)
- Walker, Thomas 1936-1948, 12 items (Box 133)
- Wallace, Henry 1934-1935, 2 items (Box 133)
- Walpole, Hugh 1939, 2 items (Box 133)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Walpole
- Walsh, Chad 1941-1953, 19 items (Box 133)
- Walter, Eugene n.d., 1 l. (Box 133)
- Wang, C.T. 1938 July 12, 1 l. (Box 133)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Wang
- Wanger, Walter, Rep. of 1940, 8 items (Box 133)
- Ward, Barbara 1950, 3 items (Box 133)
- Ward, Mary Dearing 1938, 4 items (Box 133)
- Warren, Robert Penn 1936-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 133)
- Wasson, Theodore 1939 June 14, 1 l. (Box 133)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Wasson
- Watkins, Ann, Inc. 1937-1953, ca. 150 items (Box 133)
- Watson, Archibald 1924-1934, 23 items (Box 133)
- Watson, Forbes 1939 March 3, 1 l. (Box 133)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Watson
- Watson, W.O. 1924-1929, 4 items (Box 133)
- Watt, A.S. 1938-1939, 5 items (Box 133)
- Watt, Homer 1939, 2 items (Box 133)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Watt
- Watts, Stephen 1924-1939, 3 items (Box 133)
- Waymack, William Wesley 1946-1953, 36 items (Box 133)
- Weaver, William 1945-1951, 14 items (Box 133)
- Webb, Margaret 1950, 8 items (Box 133)
- Webb, Walter Prescott 1938-1953, 5 items (Box 133)
- Wecter, Dixon 1936-1946, 33 items (Box 133)
- Weddell, Alexander 1939-1947, 10 items (Box 133)
- Weedon, William 1937-1954, 41 items (Box 133)
- Weeks, Donald 1946-1947, 6 items (Box 133)